export const QUESTIONS = {
    1: {
        question: "What is Sam's favourite anime?",
        answer: 1
    },
    2: {
        question: "What is Sam's favourite programming language?",
        answer: 3,
    },
    3: {
        question: "What is the first programming language Sam learned?",
        answer: 0
    },
    4: {
        question: "Who is Sam's favourite artist?",
        answer: 2
    },
    5: {
        question: "What did Sam play that allowed him to tour Ontario?",
        answer: 2
    },
    6: {
        question: "Where does Sam currently work?",
        answer: 1
    },
    7: {
        question: "Where does Sam go to school?",
        answer: 3,
    },
    8: {
        question: "How often does Sam write code?",
        answer: 0
    },
    9: {
        question: "What is Sam currently building?",
        answer: 2
    },
    10: {
        question: "What is Sam's favourite concerto?",
        answer: 1
    }
}

export const OPTIONS = {
    1: [
        "Attack on Titan",
        "JoJos Bizarre Adventure",
        "Erased",
        "Jujutsu Kaisen"
    ],
    2: [
        "C++",
        "Java",
        "JavaScript",
        "Python"
    ],
    3: [
        "Python",
        "C++",
        "JavaScript",
        "Ruby"
    ],
    4: [
        "Tyler the Creator",
        "Childish Gambino",
        "Frank Ocean",
        "Scary Pockets"
    ],
    5: [
        "Piano",
        "League of Legends",
        "Trumpet",
        "Saxophone"
    ],
    6: [
        "Unemployed",
        "Ford, Autonomous Vehicles",
        "Idk but I want to hire him",
        "Somewhere on Mars"
    ],
    7: [
        "University of Toronto",
        "Zoom University",
        "Stanford",
        "University of Waterloo"
    ],
    8: [
        "Every day",
        "Once every 3 years",
        "Whenever his PM yells at him",
        "Too often"
    ],
    9: [
        "Some React site",
        "A table",
        "An autonomous drone",
        "An ikea shelf"
    ],
    10: [
        "Horn Concerto in D Major K.412: Allegro",
        "Tchaikovskiy: Violin Concerto in D Major",
        "Haydn: Trumpet Concerto in Eb Major",
        "Rondeau in Eb Major"
    ]
}